foreign
I'm too embarrassed to mention these
things to the extent that I didn't
mention it in the introduction that I
should have I probably would in the next
Edition this happens to be a translation
number 19 in English
this is the 19th translation
the list of the translations from Beirut
you read it in Beirut where they had a
list of all the English stuff they
and so this is another scientist so many
signs that they had this God showered Me
With Science that this is an authorized
that God approves of this
and
that they should not have any hesitation
about
and the time closes day after day I have
a lesson on my desk that came today from
a prisoner to his property illiterate
you can tell from the way he's writing
the letter
and he was telling me that we lost this
Quran somebody told this Quran from him
and then he's the same house
he expresses it because it is easy to
understand
and he had a yosefully translation
but it's not very difficult the the
archaic and classic English to musically
it's a very good translation but the
English is not
available to everybody
and Islam like any other religion
is the first when it comes to a new land
is first embraced by the Opera
and the poor
and these are the best people
they end up being the best people
so this fellow is in prison with
practically illiterate but God made the
Quran available to help grow the
distances that's just one example you
want to see the letter I have it to know
that
so these lessons am
where our signs to death translation it
has the name of the mark of 2000 in the
front
is the authorized English version of
Quran
you you noticed Latifah's emotion and
uh
prayers of my person has once was
talking about their translation he is
reacting to something that's been
happening
continuously when they argue with you or
discuss with you the issue of Quran and
Hadith and who God the Lord I Do Worship
they make a classic statement
that you're idolizing
this is classic
and they know that the prophet wanted to
go and pick him up oh God shoot him or
something here but this is the classic
lion that they always say you are
idolizing yourself today for the
worshiping yourself
or whatever they want to say
but uh I'm going to address this issue
in details
but I'm going to mention a role of thumb
that will tell us exactly who is
worshiping whom
I mean you can use that as a Criterion
for yourself and for any of anybody else
I want you to open turana in verse 31.
I'm going to repeat this in my photo
okay so that's what you promised not to
fall as fall asleep in my next photo or
when I let you see all these things
Surah 9 verse 31
the top of fed 129
says they have taken their priests and
rabbis as Lords besides God
for God besides God
as well as Christ the son of Mary
they were commanded not to worship but
the one God there is no God except he
is not too glorious to have Partners now
I wanted to notice the first part of the
verse they have taken their priests and
rabbis as Lords beside gods
Muhammad
and it applies to every congregation
every religion we have taken their
Scholars their imams their priests and
their revised as God beside God
how
did they do that I was supposed to
worship God Alone
but how did they take their Scholars the
imams and the priests and the rabbis as
God besides God
what is the criteria and this is what I
want you to never forget
the Criterion is
if the scholar or the priest or the
rabbi or the scholar is saying something
that is identical to What God Says
then you are not watching the ocean
worshiping God so God said you said obey
God the messenger and those in charge
among you on the imams among you
for that matter among you because of
your believer
because they utter the same things that
God is uttering
however if the Imam or the priest or the
rabbi
or the scholar says something that is
different from what God says if you
follow that
then you are worshiping this Imam or
this priest is this scholar or this
Rabbi if he says something that is
different from what God Said
a good example
it was last night
went to the MSA last night and they were
having a quranic study
and then the middle of the chronic
studies yeah he said the least brother
can I ask you a question
and the brother said
go ahead so he said
how come you pray the noon
and the afternoon silently when there's
a commandment from God that used to mock
pray silently
if you cannot pray loudly stood out or
too long but seek an intermediate tone
so they gave him a long spin about the
Hadith and the Sunnah and the scholars
now here is an example to where the
scholar said something different from
what God Said
and then you are given the freedom of
choice I want to choose the word of God
or the word of the scholar or the Imam
the Imam is saying pray the noon and the
afternoon silence you and God says do
not pray silently
this is in Surah 17 verse 110 do not try
side of it you shall not pray silently
very clear commandment
now the person
here makes a choice he's going to
worship God worship the amen
because here we have a difference okay
so the Criterion is
if the Imam or the priest or the rabbi
for the scholar is saying something that
is identical to what God Said then you
are worshiping God because God said that
is saying you shall worship God Alone
if you don't obey that what does it mean
it means you will not worship God Alone
and therefore you go to hell
but you have to obey that because he is
saying something that is identical to
what God Said and you are not worshiping
the man in that case you're worshiping
God because he is uttering the words of
God
or Commandments identical to what God
commanded
so uh
asked them he said well whose words do
you follow I know do you follow the
words of God or the word for somebody
who says that the prophet said
listen there
so the they told them you don't have
permission to speak
he said oh what a problem here
you know they found out I mean obviously
they uh they had no
uh reply to this I mean he's he's coming
very strong with that commanded on his
side and probably 2010 that we couldn't
see you know what happened
but the Box didn't want him to go
away
[Music]
from this problem
so much I had said I mean we're here
discussing Quran and religion and I
don't say why I need permission to speak
when everybody was having a discussion
here so they said okay the whole thing
is over
and they finished everything and they
got something left
but so this is this is the Criterion
let's look up again at the top of page
129.
they have taken their priests and rabbis
as Lords or God beside God
and this is what the Muslims did
in unmasked
by the middle he fell in certain steps
and they have taken their Scholars and
imams as God beside God
because they said things that are
different from what God Said and these
people followed the scholars
to their worshiping
I mean you follow the words of your God
you follow the words of the scholars the
worship him to come if you follow the
words of the image that are different
from what God said you're worshiping the
amen but this is a classic line
if you are
very
much
at this time
foreign
problems
and um
that's a big mistake
that was the first book
what it was time to do when he thought
I'm gonna shift out the things that
don't make sense
what he said in his book is this
probably what the prophet said yeah
I try to
understand
whatever the Quran says
today
then
there is something
good for it yeah
uh going back East results
you can always see the first ottoman
church or the church before that they
never I never saw so far leaving all
kinds of kind of books that they talk
about Muhammad they've talked about
Allah thought but nobody else this is
you this is
greatly but no well you know of course
have you control a good bit into turkey
but I have to admit
Amendment
but the more when you move
tips and questions
and everything on the buses and the
shops
always
like saying God
like uh
the same thing like in Christianity with
Jesus
so this is where the people is coming
from because it's been
this has been there
the lion but they have been moving but
because they're collecting and they've
been here I guess all the time
however it comes to distinguish
and maybe maybe you are worship them how
do you know if this is the Criterion
that you know
in other words if I say something that
is different from what God said they're
going to listen to me or listen to God's
word you just you can tell that you are
worshiping God worshiping me
by that material
emperor
as you know I wouldn't dare say anything
that's different from what God Said
you won't let me get away with it
as long as it conforms with the Quran
and you accept it when you will not want
to do this but if I share something that
is different
something different it is your duty to
certainly this is rubbish
yeah
and this is what we do here I mean look
at God looking at me I wouldn't dare say
something wrong
I would
thank God
well this is uh
these are heavy yeah
it's our time that this translation is
also right
and they wouldn't I wouldn't trade with
otherwise
I was very demanding and thank God I was
I saw so many signs maybe someday I
would write in there I mentioned a lot
of them to a lot of you
but you know it's an awesome
responsibility because if I if I write
one sentence here that is wrong
and I mislead the hundred people
I will get it possible for that
and if you don't mind I'm the biggest
chicken around here
I don't want any uh anybody else who
thinks I'm gonna have enough of my own
so I don't want to mislead to anybody
I'm carrying
anybody else
missed driving
so the responsibility is awesome
and uh
without comparing with Moses or anything
if you remember modern was very
reluctant God said I'm shooting about my
messenger I wanted to go and deliver the
message to her and he said so I don't
even have to talk
and God said okay I'm gonna set the air
send Aaron with you and you say uh well
I committed murder in that country and
I'm afraid they will get me
he was not making up outside of Mexico
because it's an awesome responsibility
a m
I don't think we even comprehend the
significance
of these this is the the opposition is
beginning to
realize what the significance is
and now there's a conspiracy of Silence
because
instead of attacking as they used to now
they are just completely side
so it is going to overwhelm them to Zone
to overtake them whether they like it or
not but this is God's miracle not
because I had anything to do with it
because it had nothing to do with it
thank you
the new book you see the new book
everybody see the new book
that new book is gonna demonstrated
let me get it in fact
we just have one coffee here
okay
this thing is happening
what this book is showing you is the
visual impresentation of this nerve
where I had for example in this store or
a l m
well I couldn't do it in this store
because a m is very very frequent level
so I marked the letter to the son not
the Alm but all the other methods
so they can see
for themselves how many letters are
there you can see the count
the book before this the computer speaks
with all numbers
and to be honest with you I don't blame
them for not believing the numbers
especially on the other
uh skeptical and everything else
but this year will force the issue on
them what can they say there's nothing
they can say
the council there
but I told you about the fellows from
Nigeria who wrote and said
there are 56 views in chapter two
and how they repeated it and really
repeated it and they have the group of
people do it and every time they come up
for 56.
and all I did was make a year of copy of
that
welcome to them never heard from them
didn't even write them say yeah you're
right
we were talking about
I was turning over to Adventure last
night
foreign
[Music]
you're wondering
what is here
no uh no
after Alm you notice the third material
of God Among the one God
because all these numbers are based
on the number 19 which means
God is the one right
all these methods without exception
every single one of them
are multiples of 19 and 19 means God has
won verse 19 means one
so
in other words God Is providing the
meaning of these letters
who may be able to resume the Arabic
language
tomorrow morning
and when you didn't get to the numbers
but we will maybe tomorrow
but the one
the word one in Arabic is Russian
and the performance is wild NFL there
and go ahead
and when the Quran came down there were
no numbers
the alphabet was used on numbers
and one was six before they invented the
numbers the letter Y was six
Melissa Eric Was Won six and one is
seven right
the third letter hand was eight
one
six and if one high is eight where I had
so six and one is seven and eight is
fifteen then
was four
15 and 4 is 19. so the word
was 19.
19 million God is one so a l m
means god is one so that's the meaning
of the first left
something
nobody ever knew before this this group
I had three people here who are kind of
the three people that were implant about
not using the naval body in our events
they were
I don't know what the occasion was but I
think they wanted everyone to be experts
in Arabic first
in order to understand the Quran
and they exported to them Surah 41 verse
44 that says you do not need Arabic but
if you're a believer
the only requirement is to be a believer
and doesn't put the Quran in your heart
and just to
demonstrate to them
but what God Said is the truth let's see
if it happened to be sitting next to us
and I thought that there is a Muslims
that
relatively new and you can ask her
anything about Quran
go ahead and ask her anything about
Quran and see if the Quran is in her
house or not
so they thought of the hardest most
difficult most impossible question
and they told the people okay tell us
the meaning of
k-h-y-a-s at the beginning of Surah 19.
and Latifah said I thought you would
never ask
[Laughter]
you know
but they were really that uh
it was a great demonstration for them
they didn't argue after that
and I think something could happen to
them however they disappeared I don't
know what would that may be a good side
foreign
[Music]
you see how the numbering of the verse
comes in the middle of the statement
this is the this is a continual sentence
but the number of reverse
came into Maybe
indicating a deliberate
numbering of the vertices
as you know part of this code
was that the first Surah and the other
Revelation consists of 19 verses
so that's a deliberate system
if anybody played around with that that
fact would disappear
foreign
consists of 19 verses
and you will see it in this book
this box that they had inshallah in a
week or so 10 days
there is another book that's called
Quran Hadith and Islam to also will
cover the issues Hadith
and we will not be Applause never again
when they discussed the Quran Hadith
globalizing we discovered that to help
the blue line here in the office and I
met them this morning
to get a monthly they read the book on
Monday or Tuesday
and they will hold this book until the
another book is also very when we would
say from both
in the middle of the week
it's gonna happen here so we'll have
some good exercise and we probably
invent another national anthem
as we unload the book
but that book would show you a little
bit of the first floor and the older
Revelations consists of 19 verses
and you see the copy of it
so he revealed the Torah and the gospel
previously is a continual sentence
is
to guide the people he revealed the
statute book
that your book meaning the book of law
Lord these are God's laws
we have to obey this law
if you are to have a perfect life